A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "Haloperidol in Psychiatry", 17:3, 1975 January 31 (Box 319, Folder 8-13, Box 320, Folder 1-2)
- "Shock, Therapy (Vasoactive Agents): Dopamine for Treatment of Shock", 17:4, 1975 February 14 (Box 320, Folder 3-7)
- "Meningitis: Initial Treatment of Meningitis in Children", 17:4, 1975 February 14 (Box 320, Folder 8-12)
- "Pain: Traction for Neck and Low-Back Disorders", 17:4, 1975 February 14 (Box 320, Folder 13-14, Box 321, Folder 1-2)
- "Medical Letter: Misuse of the Medical Letter", 17:4, 1975 February 14 (Box 321, Folder 3-4)
- "Drug Interactions: Adverse Interactions of Drugs", 17:5, 1975 February 28 (Box 321, Folder 5-10)
- "Aspirin: Can Aspirin Prevent Myocardial Infarction", 17:6, 1975 March 14 (Box 321, Folder 11-15)
- "Contraceptives, Intrauterine (Copper): CU-7, A Copper-Containing IUD", 17:6, 1975 March 14 (Box 321, Folder 16, Box 322, Folder 1-8)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices: Ocusert", 17:6, 1975 March 14 (Box 322, Folder 9-15)
- "Benzodiazepines (Flurazepam): Flurazepam (Dalmane) ", 17:7, 1975 March 28 (Box 323, Folder 1-7, 7A)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (Blood); Drug-Induced Bone Marrow Depression", 17:7, 1975 March 28 (Box 323, Folder 8-9, Box 324, Folder 1-3)
- "Parkinson's Disease, Levodopa: Drug Therapy for Parkinson's Disease", 17:8, 1975 April 11 (Box 324, Folder 4-9)
- "Parenteral Equipment: I. V. Filters", 17:8, 1975 April 11 (Box 325, Folder 1-7)
- "Parasitic Infections (Drugs for): Mebendazole - A New Anthelmintic", 17:9, 1975 April 25 (Box 325, Folder 8-13)
- "Psoriasis: Photochemotherapy of Psoriasis", 17:9, 1975 April 25 (Box 326, Folder 1-6)
- "Tetracyclines, Side Effects: Adverse Effects of Minocycline", 17:9, 1975 April 25 (Box 326, Folder 7-12)
- "Wounds and Injuries: Drugs for Athletic Injuries", 17:10, 1975 May 9 (Box 326, Folder 13-15, Box 327, Folder 1-3)
- "Cancer, Chemotherapy: Doxorubican (Adriamycin) - A New Anticancer Drug", 17:10, 1975 May 9 (Box 327, Folder 4-10)
- "Plastics: Plastic Containers for Intravenous Solutions", 17:10, 1975 May 9 (Box 327, Folder 11-12, Box 328, Folder 1-3)
- "Hypertension, Therapy: Clonidine (Catapres) for Hypertension", 17:11, 1975 May 23 (Box 328, Folder 4-11)
- "Corticosteroids, Topical: Halcinonide (Halog) - Another New Topical Steroid", 17:11, 1975 May 23 (Box 328, Folder 12, Box 329, Folder 1-4)
- "Antimicrobials, Prophylactic Use (Surgery): Antimicrobial Prophylaxis for Orthopedic Operations", 17:11, 1975 May 23 (Box 329, Folder 5-7)
- "Lipids, Drug Reduction: Lipid-Lowering Drugs", 17:12, 1975 June 6 (Box 329, Folder 8, Box 330, Folder 1-7)
- "Skin Diseases, Therapy: Tetracyclines for Acne", 17:12, 1975 June 6 (Box 330, Folder 8-12, Box 331, Folder 1)
- "Poison Ivy and Oak: Hyposensitization to Poison Ivy", 17:12, 1975 June 6 (Box 331, Folder 2-7)
- "Metronidazole: Is Flagyl Dangerous?", 17:13, 1975 June 20 (Box 331, Folder 8-13)
- "Penicillin Allergy: Tests for Penicillin Allergy" and "Penicillin Allergy: Testing for Penicillin Allergy with Aqueous Penicillin G-Caution". 17:13, and 17:20, 1975 June 20; 1975 September 26 (Box 332, Folder 1-5)
- "Otitis Media: Treatment of Acute Otitis Media", 17:13, 1975 June 20 (Box 332, Folder 6-12, Box 333, Folder 1)
- "Angina Pectoris: Drugs for Prophylaxis of Angina Pectoris", 17:14, 1975 July 4 (Box 333, Folder 2-9, Box 334, Folder 1-2)
- "Schizophrenia: Molindone - A New Antipsychotic Drug", 17:14, 1975 July 4 (Box 334, Folder 3-7)
- "Diagnostic Tests (Gastrointestinal): Pentagastrin", 17:14, 1975 July 4 (Box 334, Folder 8-13)
- "Sweeteners, Artificial: Synthetic Sweeteners: Cyclamates, Saccharin, Aspartame", 17:15, 1975 July 18 (Box 334, Folder 14, Box 335, Folder 1-6)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Mitomycin (Mutamycin)", 17:15, 1975 July 18 (Box 335, Folder 7-12)
- "Fever: Drug Fever", 17:15, 1975 July 18 (Box 335, Folder 13-14, Box 336, Folder 1-4)
- "Cancer, Tests: Mammography", 17:16, 1975 August 1 (Box 336, Folder 5-10)
- "Ulcers: Carbenoxolone Sodium for Gastric Ulcer", 17:16, 1975 August 1 (Box 336, Folder 11, Box 337, Folder 1-5)
- "Phenothiazines (Mesoridazine): Serentil for Chronic Brain Syndrome", 17:16, 1975 August 1 (Box 337, Folder 6-11)
- "Vitamin E", 17:17, 1975 August 15 (Box 337, Folder 12-16, Box 338, Folder 1-3)
- "Gastrointestinal System Diseases: Colonoscopy", 17:17, 1975 August 15 (Box 338, Folder 4-9)
- "Potassium: Who Needs Slow-Release Potassium Tablets?", 17:18, 1975 August 29 (Box 338, Folder 10-14)
- "Pacemakers, Artificial: New Developments in Cardiac Pacemakers", 17:18, 1975 August 29 (Box 339, Folder 1-7)
- "Carbamazepine in the Management of Seizure Disorders", 17:18, 1975 August 29 (Box 339, Folder 8-12, Box 340, Folder 1)
- "Fungal Infection: Clotrimazole (Lotrimin) - A New Topical Antifungal Drug", 17:19, 1975 September 12 (Box 340, Folder 2-7)
- "Hypertension, Therapy: Combipres for Hypertension"; 17:19, 1975 September 12 (Box 340, Folder 8-13)
- "Gastrointestinal Flatulence: Simethicone for Discomfort Caused by Gastrointestinal Gas", 17:19, 1975 September 12 (Box 340, Folder 14-16, Box 341, Folder 1-4)
- "Asthma, Drugs for: Terbutaline for Asthma", 17:20, 1975 September 26 (Box 341, Folder 5-10, Box 342, Folder 1)
- "Hypertension, Therapy: Sodium Nitropusside for Hypertensive Crisis", 17:20, 1975 September 26 (Box 342, Folder 2-7)
- "Tobramycin: Tobramycin Sulfate (Nebcin) ", 17:21, 1975 October 10 (Box 342, Folder 8-11, Box 343, Folder 1-3)
- "Diuretics (Spironolactone): Spironolactone, A Reassessment", 17:21, 1975 October 10 (Box 343, Folder 4-7)
- "Asthma, Drugs for: Steroid Aerosols for Asthma", 17:21, 1975 October 10 (Box 343, Folder 8-11)
- "Cold Remedies: Oral Cold Remedies", 17:22, 1975 October 24 (Box 343, Folder 12, Box 344, Folder 1-6)
- "Influenza: Influenza Vaccine for 1975-1976", 17:22, 1975 October 24 (Box 344, Folder 7-11)
- "Nutrition and Diet (Fiber): The High Fiber Diet: Its Effect on the Bowel", 17:23, 1975 November 7 (Box 344, Folder 12, Box 345, Folder 1-4)
- "Corticosteroids: Alternate-Day Corticosteroid Therapy", 17:23, 1975 November 7 (Box 345, Folder 5-9)
- "Bone: Calcitonin in the Treatment of Paget's Disease", 17:24, 1975 November 21 (Box 345, Folder 10, Box 346, Folder 1-3)
- "Corticosteroids: Oral Corticosteroids", 17:24, 1975 November 21 (Box 346, Folder 4-8)
- "Urinary Tract Infections (Treatment): Trimethoprim-Sulfamethoxazole for Urinary Tract Infections", 7:25, 1975 December 5 (Box 346, Folder 9-12, Box 347, Folder 1-2)
- "Schizophrenia: Loxapine (Loxitane)", 17:25, 1975 December 5 (Box 347, Folder 3-10, Box 348, Folder 1)
- "Diarrhea: Lomotil for Control of Diarrhea in Children", 17:25, 1975 December 5 (Box 348, Folder 2-7)
- "Lidocaine: Prophylactic Use of Lidocaine in Myocardial Infarction", 18:1, 1976 January 2 (Box 348, Folder 8-12)
- "Urinary Tract Infections (Treatment): Oxolinic Acid"; 18:1, 1976 January 2 (Box 349, Folder 1-5)
- "Liver Diseases: Lactulose for Hepatic Encephalopathy", 18:1, 1976 January 2 (Box 349, Folder 6-10)
- "Hyperactivity, Child: Pemoline (Cylert) for Minimal Brain Dysfunction", 18:2, 1976 January 16 (Box 349, Folder 11-14, Box 350, Folder 1-2)
- "Psoriasis: Azaribine (Triazure) for Severe Psoriasis", 18:2, 1976 January 16 (Box 350, Folder 3-9)
- "Antimicrobials: The Choice of Antimicrobial Drugs", 18:3, 1976 January 30 (Box 350, Folder 10-11, Box 351, Folder 1-4)
- "Griseofulvin: A New Formulation and Some Old Concerns", 18:4, 1976 February 13 (Box 351, Folder 5-10)
- "Epilepsy: Clonazepam: A New Anticonvulsant", 18:4, 1976 February 13 (Box 351, Folder 11-12, Box 352, Folder 1-3)
- "Reserpine: Severe Depression Caused by Reserpine" and "Correction: Dosage of Oxolinic Acid", 18:4, 1976 February 13 (Box 352, Folder 4-8)
- "Contraceptives, Oral (Side Effects): Serious Adverse Effects of Oral Contraceptives and Estrogens", 18:5, 1976 February 27 (Box 352, Folder 9, Box 353, Folder 1-7)
- "Phenyton (Diphenylhydantoin)", 18:5, 1976 February 27 (Box 353, Folder 8-10, Box 354, Folder 1-4)
- "Epilepsy: Treatment for Epilepsy", 18:6, 1976 March 12 (Box 354, Folder 5-8, Box 355, Folder 1-5)
- "Gonoccocal Infections: Treatment of Syphilis and Gonorrhea", Consultants: M.L. Drafts, 18:7, and "Gonoccoal Infections: Prophylactic Treatment of Syphilis and Gonorrhea - Dosage Correction" Consultants: M. L. Drafts, 18:10, 1976 March 26 1976 May 7 (Box 355, Folder 6-7)
- "Drug Interaction: Foods Potentially Harmful to Patients Taking MAO Inhibitors", 18:7, 1976 March 26 (Box 355, Folder 8-12)
- "Manufacturer's Information on Nalfon", 1976 April 5 (Box 356, Folder 1)
- "Cephalosporins: The Cephalosporins", 18:8, 1976 April 9 (Box 356, Folder 2-7)
- "Diagnostic Tests: Screening Newborn Infants for Cystic Fibrosis", 18:8, 1976 April 9 (Box 356, Folder 8-14)
- "Nitroglycerin: Nitroglycerin in Acute Myocardial Infarction", 18:9, 1976 April 23 (Box 356, Folder 15, Box 357, Folder 1-3)
- "Cerebrovascular Disorders: Drugs for the Improvement of Cerebral Function in the Elderly", 18:9, 1976 April 23 (Box 357, Folder 4-8)
- "Parasitic Infections (Drugs for): Treatment of Giardiasis", 18:9, 1976 April 23 (Box 357, Folder 9-13)
- "Propranolol: Should Propranolol be Stopped Before Surgery", 18:10, 1976 May 7 (Box 358, Folder 1-4)
- "Alcohol: Ethanol in the Treatment of the Threatened Premature Labor", 18:10, 1976 May 7 (Box 358, Folder 5-7)
- "Urinary Tract Infections (Treatment): Sulfacytine", 18:10, 1976 May 7 (Box 358, Folder 8-12)
- "Estrogens: The 'New' Estrogens: Are They Safer", 18:11, 1976 May 21 (Box 359, Folder 1-7)
- "Pentazocine: Re-Evaluation of Parenteral Pentazocine", 18:11, 1976 May 21 (Box 359, Folder 8-10, Box 360, Folder 1-3)
- "Pentazocine: Oral Pentazocine in New Talwin Compound", 18:11, 1976 May 21 (Box 360, Folder 4-8)
- "Gout: Drugs for Gout", 18:12, 1976 June 4 (Box 360, Folder 9-14)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices: Lightcast II", 18:12, 1976 June 4 (Box 361, Folder 1-5)
- "Lipids, Drugs Reduction: Dextrothyroxine for Lowering Cholesterol", 18:13, 1976 June 18 (Box 361, Folder 6-10)
- "Diabetes, Therapy: Glyburide", 18:13, 1976 June 18 (Box 361, Folder 11-15, Box 362, Folder 1)
- "Headache: Drugs for Migraine", 18:13, 1976 June 18 (Box 362, Folder 2-9, Box 363, Folder 1-2)
- "Cardiovascular Disease (Tests): Coronary Arteriography and Coronary Artery Surgery", 18:14, 1976 July 2 (Box 363, Folder 3-8, Box 364, Folder 1)
- "Corticosteroids: Prenatal Glucocorticoids for Prevention of the Respiratory Distress Syndrome", 18:14, 1976 July 2 (Box 364, Folder 2-5)
- "Benzodiazepines: Benzodiazepine Overdosage"; 18:14, 1976 July 2 (Box 364, Folder 6-7)
- "Influenza: Swine Influenza Vaccine" Consultants; 18:15, 1976 July 16 (Box 364, Folder 8-11)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (Eye): Adverse Ocular Effects of Systemic Drugs", 18:15, 1976 July 16 (Box 364, Folder 12, Box 365, Folder 1-9)
- "Contraceptives, Intrauterine: Progestasert - A New Intrauterine Contraceptive Device", 18:16, 1976 July 30 (Box 366, Folder 1-6)
- "Vaginal Disease: Gyne-Lotrimin for Vaginal Infections", 18:16, 1976 July 30 (Box 366, Folder 7-10, Box 367, Folder 1-2)
- "Hypertension Therapy: Cyanide Intoxication from Sodium Nitroprusside in Anesthesia", 18:16, 1976 July 30 (Box 367, Folder 3-7)
- "Marijuana: Marijuana", 18:17, 1976 August 13 (Box 367, Folder 8-12, Box 368, Folder 1)
- "Eye Disease: Drugs for Bacterial Conjunctivitis", 18:17, 1976 August 13 (Box 368, Folder 2-6)
- "Acetaminophen: Acetaminophen", 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 368, Folder 7-10, Box 369, Folder 1-2)
- "Cancer, Chemical Carcinogenesis: Carcinogenicity of Drugs in Small Animals and Mutagenity in Bacteria: Does it Make Sense", 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 3-6)
- "Asthma, Drugs for Beclomethasone Dipropionate (Vanceril) for Asthma", 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 7-11)
- "Rheumatism and Arthritis (Chemotherapy): New Drugs for Arthritis", 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 369, Folder 12-16, Box 370, Folder 1-4)
- "X-Rays: Computed Tomography", 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 370, Folder 5-9)
- "Lipids: Margarines and Other Dietary Facts", 18:20, 1976 September 24 (Box 371, Folder 1-5)
- "Cancer Immunology: Immunotherapy for Malignant Disease" Consultants, 18:20, 1976 September 24 (Box 371, Folder 6-10, Box 372, Folder 1-2)
- "Antiseptics: Chlorhexidine and Other Antiseptics", 18:21, 1976 October 8 (Box 372, Folder 3-7, Box 373, Folder 1-2)
- "Diarrhea: Travelers' Diarrhea - New Developments", 18:21, 1976 October 8 (Box 373, Folder 3-5)
- "Psychopharmacological Agents: Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders", 18:22, 1976 October 22 (Box 373, Folder 6-9, Box 374, Folder 1-6)
- "Amikacin: Amikacin" Consultants, 18:23, 1976 November 5 (Box 374, Folder 7-9, Box 375, Folder 1-2)
- "Osteoporosis: Osteoporosis", 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 375, Folder 3-8)
- "Fungal Infections: Drugs for Athlete's Foot and Tinea Cruris" Basic Source Check-List, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 375, Folder 9-11, Box 376, Folder 1-3)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Lomustine (CeeNU)", 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 4-8)
- "Nutrition and Diet (Infants): Soy-Based Formula for Infants", 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 9-13)
- "ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH: Treatment of frostbite", 18:105, 1976 December 3 (Box 377, Folder 1-3)
- "EYE DISEASE: Treatment of diabetic retinopathy", 18:107, 1976 December 3 (Box 377, Folder 4-6)
- "HEMORRHOIDS: Preparation H; " 18:108, 1976 December 3 (Box 377, Folder 7)
- "CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY: cancer chemotherapy", 18:109, and Correction, 19:20, 1976 December 17; 1977 February 25 (Box 377, Folder 8, Box 378, Folder 1-6)
- "PARKINSON'S DISEASE, CHEMOTHERAPY: New drugs for Parkinson's Disease", 18:117, 1976 December 31 (Box 378, Folder 7-10, Box 379, Folder 1)
- "RHEUMATISM & ARTHRITIS (Chemotherapy) Arthropan liquid & other salicylates for Arthritis", 18:119, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 2-6)
- "ANABOLIC AGENTS: Anabolic steroids for athletes", 18:120, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 7-11)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Prazosin (mini press) for hypertension", 19:1, 1977 January 14 (Box 379, Folder 12, Box 380, Folder 1-5)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Prevention of serious infections after splenectomy", 19:2, 1977 January 14 (Box 380, Folder 6-9)
- "ANESTHETICS, LOCAL: Long - Acting Local Anesthetics", 19:4, 1977 January 14 (Box 380, Folder 10-11, Box 381, Folder 1-6)
- "DRUG INTERACTION: adverse interactions of drugs", 19:5, 1977 January 28 (Box 381, Folder 7-10)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE - OVERDOSE): Diagnosis & Management of reactions to drug abuse", 19:13, 1977 February 11 (Box 381, Folder 11-12, Box 382, Folder 1-4)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Ticarcillin", 19:17, 1977 February 25 (Box 382, Folder 5-8)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (Drugs for): Kwell & other drugs for treatment of lice & scabies", 19:18, 1977 February 25 (Box 382, Folder 9, Box 383, Folder 1-4)
- "COSMETICS: Drysol for treatment of hyperhidrosis", 19:20, 1977 February 25 (Box 383, Folder 5-10)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Drugs for hypertension", 19:21, 1977 March 11 (Box 383, Folder 11-12, Box 384, Folder 1-4)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY (PHENFORMIN): Phenformin", 19:25, 1977 March 25 (Box 384, Folder 5-9)
- "ABORTION: Relative safety of mid-trimester abortion methods", 19:25, 1977 March 25 (Box 384, Folder 10-13)
- "ANALGESICS: Sedation & analgesia for minor painful procedures", 19:26, 1977 March 25 (Box 385, Folder 1-5)
- "HEMOSTATICS: Avitene a new topical hemostatic agent" ("CORRECTION: Sodium in ticarcillin and Carbenicillin"), 19:28, 1977 March 25 (Box 385, Folder 6-10)
- "ULCERS: Cimetidine - an investigational drug for the treatment of duodenal ulcer", 19:29, 1977 April 8 (Box 385, Folder 11, Box 386, Folder 1-4)
- "HEPARIN: Administration & Monitoring of heparin therapy", 19:31, 1977 April 8 (Box 386, Folder 5-9)
- "SPORTS: Management of tennis elbow", 19:33, 1977 April 22 (Box 387, Folder 1-3)
- "IRON: Adverse effects of parenteral iron", 19:35, 1977 April 22 (Box 387, Folder 4-8)
- "GALL BLADDER: Sincalide for cholecystography", 19:36, 1977 April 22 (Box 388, Folder 1-5)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Antimicrobials, prophylaxis: prevention of wound infection & sepsis after surgery", 19:37, 1977 May 6 (Box 388, Folder 6-10, Box 389, Folder 1-3)
- "LIPIDS, DRUG REDUCTION (PROBUCOL): Probucol for hypercholesterolemia", 19:41, 1977 May 20 (Box 389, Folder 4-8)
- "VIRALINFECTION (HERPES): Vidarabine (vira-A), 19:42, 1977 May 20 (Box 389, Folder 9, Box 390, Folder 1-4)
- "RABIES: A new rabies vaccine", 19:43, 1977 May 20 (Box 390, Folder 5-8)
- "LAXATIVES & CATHARTICS: Safety of stool softeners", 19:45, 1977 June 3 (Box 390, Folder 9-11, Box 391, Folder 1)
- "LIPIDS, DRUG REDUCTION: Hypolipidemic agents & gallstones", 19:46, 1977 June 3 (Box 391, Folder 2-5)
- "DRUG INTERACTION: Interaction with alcohol with drugs", 19:47, 1977 June 3 (Box 391, Folder 6-10)
- "BENZODIAZEPINES: Choice of benzodiazepines for treatment of anxiety or insomnia", 19:49, 1977 June 17 (Box 391, Folder 11, Box 392, Folder 1-5)
- "THYROID DISEASE: Thyroid replacement therapy", 19:50, 1977 June 17 (Box 392, Folder 6-9)
- "VIRAL INFECTIONS (HERPES): Herpes simplex & cervical carcinoma", 19:52, 1977 June 17 (Box 393, Folder 1-5)
- "METHYLPHENIDATE: Methylphenidate (Ritalin) & other drugs for treatment of hyperactive children", 19:53, 1977 July 1 (Box 393, Folder 6-9, Box 394, Folder 1-2)
- "MEDICAL EQUIPMENT & DEVICES: Devices for monitoring blood pressure at home", 19:55, 1977 July 1 (Box 394, Folder 3-7)
- "PITUITARY GLAND: Human growth hormone", 19:57, 1977 July 25 (Box 395, Folder 1-5)
- "KETAMINE: Ketamine", 19:58, 1977 July 15 (Box 395, Folder 6-9)
- "ERGOTAMINE & PREPARATIONS: Deapril - ST for senile dementia", 19:61, 1977 July 29 (Box 396, Folder 1-5)
- "MENSTRUATION DISORDERS: Danazol - A new drug for treatment of endometriosis", 19:62, 1977 July 29 (Box 396, Folder 6-10)
- "HAIR: Treatment of dandruff", 19:63, 1977 July 29 (Box 396, Folder 11-12, Box 397, Folder 1-3)
- "ANTIHISTAMINES" Azatadine (Optimine) - a new antihistamine", 19:77, 1977 September 23 (Box 397, Folder 4-9)
- "Benzodiazepines, Prazepam (Verstan)", 19:92, 1977 November 4 (Box 398, Folder 1-5)
- "Anticonvulsants, Sodium Valproate", 19:93, 1977 November 18 (Box 398, Folder 6-12)
- "Meningitis, Intralumbar & intraventricular therapy of bacterial meningitis", 19:94, 1977 November 18 (Box 399, Folder 1-7)
- "Quadriplegia From Trampolines" Original Manuscripts, 19:96, 1977 December 2 (Box 399, Folder 8)
- "Tuberculosis, Chemotherapy-Drugs for treatment of tuberculosis", 19:97, 1977 December 2 (Box 399, Folder 9-13)
- "Automobile Driving-Drugs and Driving", 19:99, 1977 December 2 (Box 400, Folder 1-11)
- "Arrhythias-Disopyramide (Norpace) for ventricular arrhythmias.", 19:101, 1977 December 16 (Box 401, Folder 1-8)
- "Respiratory Disease-Drugs for pneumonia; some new developments.", 19:102, 1977 December 16 (Box 401, Folder 9-12)
- "Ergotamine & Preparations - Bromocriptine", 19:103, 1977 Dec. 16 (Box 402, Folder 1-6)
- "Gonococcal Infections-Treatment of syphilis and gonorrhea", 19:105, 1977 Dec. 30 (Box 402, Folder 7-12)
- "Sleep: L-tryptophan, a "natural sedative?", 19:108, 1977 Dec. 30 (Box 403, Folder 1-8)
- "Antimicrobials-The choice of antimicrobial drugs.", 20:1, 1978 January 13 (Box 403, Folder 9-13, Box 404, Folder 1-13)
- "Hepatitis: Hepatitis B immune globulin (human)", 20:9, 1978 January 27 (Box 405, Folder 1-8)
- "Vasodilators-Drugs for ischemic peripheral disease", 20:11, 1978 January 27 (Box 405, Folder 9-14)
- "Muscle Relaxants: Flexeril - a new muscle relaxant", 20:12, 1978 January 27 (Box 406, Folder 1-7)
- "Immunization (Vaccines) Pneumococcal vaccine", 20:13, 1978 February 10 (Box 406, Folder 8-16)
- "Penicillin Allergy - Penicillin Allergy", 20:14, 1978 February 10 (Box 407, Folder 1-4)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects- Drugs causing postural hypotension", 20:15, 1978 February 10 (Box 407, Folder 5-12)
- "Parasitic Infections (Drugs For): Drugs for Parasitic Infections", 20:17, 1978 February 24 (Box 408, Folder 1-11)
- "Amantadine - Amantadine for high risk influenza", 20:25, 1978 March 10 (Box 409, Folder 1-4)
- "Diabetes Inspidus - Demopressin for diabetes insipidus", 20:26, 1978 March 10 (Box 409, Folder 5-13)
- "Sports, The use of oxygen by athletes", 20:38, 1978 March 10 (Box 409, Folder 14-18)
- "Contraceptives - The Encare Oval", 20:29, 1978 March 24 (Box 410, Folder 1-7)
- "Potassium Slow-K-Follow Up", 20:30, 1978 March 24 (Box 410, Folder 8-14)
- "Benzodiazepines - Lorazepam (Ativan)", 20:31, 1978 March 14 (Box 411, Folder 1-9)
- "Obesity-By-pass operations for obesity", 20:33, 1978 April 7 (Box 411, Folder 10-13, Box 412, Folder 1-4)
- "Skin Disease, Therapy: Topicycline-A topical tetracycline acne", 20:35, 1978 April 7 (Box 413, Folder 1-7)
- "Streptokinase: Streptokinase and Urokinae", 20:37, 1978 April 21 (Box 413, Folder 8-16)
- "Pregnancy Tests - The e.p.t. do-it-yourself early pregnancy test", 20:39, 1978 April 21 (Box 414, Folder 1-6)
- "Methadone: LAAM - a long acting methadone", 20:40, 1978 April 21 (Box 414, Folder 7-12)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Tamoxifen for breast cancer", 20:41, 1978 May 5 (Box 415, Folder 1-11)
- "Muscle Relaxants: Baclofen(Lioresal) new muscle relaxant", 20:43, 1978 May 5 (Box 416, Folder 1-9)
- "Vitamins: Vitamin B-15", 20:44, 1978 May 5 (Box 416, Folder 10-14)
- "Iron: Oral Iron", 20:45, 1978 May 19 (Box 417, Folder 1-7)
- "Wounds and Injuries Debrisan", 20:47, 1978 May 19 (Box 417, Folder 8-14)
- "Depression, Therapy Drugs for depression", 20:49, 1978 June 2 (Box 418, Folder 1-11)
- "Oxygen Hyperbaric: Hyperbaric oxygen therapy", 20:51, 1978 June 2 (Box 419, Folder 1-8)
- "Exercise, Exercise tests before exercise", 20:53, 1978 June 16 (Box 419, Folder 9-14)
- "Insect Bites and Stings: Systemic reactions to hymenoptera stings", 20:54, 1978 June 16 (Box 420, Folder 1-6)
- "Hyperactivity, Child: Feingold diet for hyperactive children", 20:55, 1978 June 16 (Box 420, Folder 7-14)
- "Zinc, Zinc", 20:57, 1978 June 30 (Box 421, Folder 1-14)
- "Otitis Media, Trimethoprim - Sulfamethoxazole for otitis media", 20:59, 1978 June 30 (Box 422, Folder 1-9)
- "Acetaminophen - Acetaminophen hepatotoxicity", 20:61, 1978 July 14 (Box 422, Folder 10-15)
- "Hypertension, Therapy: Relaxation biofeedback and exercise for the treatment of hypertension", 20:62, 1978 July 14 (Box 423, Folder 1-10)
- "Diagnostic Test 125I Fibrinogen for diagnosis of thromboembolism", 20:63 July 14, 1978 July 14 (Box 424, Folder 1-9)
- "Pregnancy (Nutrition): Nutrition in Pregnancy", 20:65, 1978 July 28 (Box 425, Folder 1-6)
- "Fungal Infections: Drugs for the Treatment of Systemic", 20:66, 1978 July 28 (Box 425, Folder 7-13)
- "Asthma DRUGS FOR: Drugs For Asthma", 20:69, 1978 August 11 (Box 426, Folder 1-10, Box 427, Folder 1-11)
- "PENICILLAMINE: Penicillamine for rheumatoid arthritis", 20:73, 1960 December 12 (Box 428, Folder 1-8)
- "AGING: Stimulants & other drugs for treatment of mental symptoms, 20:75, 1978 August 25 (Box 428, Folder 9-12)
- "DIMETHYL SUFOXIDE: Dimethyl Sulfoxide (DMSO) for interstitial cystitis", 20:76, 1978 August 25 (Box 429, Folder 13-17)
- "CIMETIDINE: Cimetinde (Tagamet); Update on Adverse Effects", 20:77, 1978 September 8 (Box 429, Folder 18-22)
- "BONE: Etidronate Disodium for Paget's Disease", 20:78, 1978 September 8 (Box 430, Folder 23-27)
- "CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY: Carmustine (BICNU)", 20:79, 1978 September 8 (Box 430, Folder 28-31, Box 431, Folder 32-33)
- "CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY: Cancer Chemotherapy", 20:81, 1978 September 22 (Box 431, Folder 34-38)
- "VASODILATORS: Use of vasodilator drugs in congestive heart failure", 20:89, 1978 October 6 (Box 432, Folder 39-44)
- "MEDICAL EQUIPMENT & DEVICES: Automated eye refraction", 20:91, 1978 October 6 (Box 432, Folder 45-49)
- "AMNIOCENTESIS: Amniocentesis in the second trimester", 20:93, 1978 October 20 (Box 432, Folder 50, Box 433, Folder 51-53)